Voices collide, the storm and the flame. Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game.
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive. In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive.
Who's afraid?
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens
You're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual
Step inside the flow
The circus of shadows
It's psyche's show
Terrible trolls in the dark
Take their stand
But angels are dancing
The psyches show terrible trolls in the dark take their stand
The angels are dan-
But it's all rehearsed, a costume disguised
Me, girl, crowned with a jagged edge
Sarcasm sharp
with the shadows
Hello, hello
Hi, let me see. Hold on one second. Let me look down all the comments. Let me say I get one second
I had a few songs play. I'm sorry. Let me check. Okay, so what do we say?
Full body cavity search? Yeah, about that time. Let me get my gloves out. One video release for every Tisa. Oh, that's not pretty nice. Why is beat-a-mad? I don't know
She's an angry angry person. I was actually over there in the chat. I was just like sitting there like saying I want to see
How goes Bronzeberg comes up. Oh the M F and F a ggot psyche. Oh, everyone hates him. He is the grifter
Yeah, well
My ex what's his name?
Here's some like some India guys
But anyway, I think he must be still in love with this guy because it's like he can't of him is Carl
He's like Carl, Carl, Carl, but anyway, so Carl like
Was mad or something last night and she's like and say it was like he's fall
I don't know. How was my fault or anything? She said, but he hates psyche. He said, oh, okay. I'm from say, okay
Oh, yeah, well, you know
No, I like him now. No, he's not always smart. He's a smart guy. And so
then she's like
Well, this thing is like, you know, Saiki is like, he's such a bottom-feeder, and, you know,
I fail to see that right now, but she will, you know, Saiki's this and that.
I'm a bottom-feeder, and she's like, and, you know, he goes when he's not wanted.
He's not wanted here, he's not wanted at Emma's.
I was like, okay, because she always is saying, oh, come to my chat, and, you know,
I'm not coming to yours, but I was, you know, even if everyone's mean.
But no one wants me there, apparently, so.
I was like, oh, thanks for letting me know no one wanted to be there, like, finally, you know, because you're always telling me, like, yeah, I want you there, but anyway, so...
And then they just, you know, attack me in the chat and stuff. I'm unmodded, and I have to unmod her again.
Eventually, I'm just a little bit lazy to do it, but I don't even care.
What's going on? I don't know. I'm dealing with a nut. It's a Puritan macadamia nut.
Let me see, I think there's no reason for you to end the stream the other day while
talking about whatever.
I know you weren't, but when I say, I don't want to talk about certain words or certain
keywords and stuff.
Don't say, no, it's okay, we're allowed to do that.
If it's your channel, then you can say, okay, I'll talk about Chernobyl and whatever all
you want.
I was like, don't talk about it, and then you kept going, and that's why I ended it,
It falls under the disrespecting psyche, or arguing psyche, and you're not supposed to argue with me.
Okay.
Why are you still consumed with me, Moshe? You know, you remember me?
You're swearing on King David's life every 20 seconds about me?
I have no idea who you are or what, like, you know.
But...
Stop being a... like a bitch.
A bitch.
She's some Yiddish.
You're convincing it
Or you day, okay
Not good
Not consumed by her. I'm just the fire is burning out. You know the fire is burning out. I was yeah
Yeah, I'm King David and on the hood. Why are you so excited? Why are you why are you making like, you know
Swearing on gods and you know neighborhoods, you know, you never even met me in real life. How are you so consumed with me?
Yeah, Moshe. Oh, okay, that's what you said about me and Peter
Well, you never met me that you're here and you're
Shalom Shalom everybody
Shalom
Yeah
Yeah, oh, oh, you know how about your schwarza. Okay, you're a schwarza and your so is your brain
Okay
Kaggle I know a little bit you just you
Anyway
I do I do enjoy Hebrew but Moshe I do not enjoy. Hi, uh, I join you with I do yeah
I do I do know a little bit of Yiddish, okay
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Okay, hi everybody, how are you doing?
Let's see Nain, Ezekiah Mater, he says Shparta, so your mother is a what? Your mother's a black something ever, but yeah
Oh, yo mama joke, so you're really original, okay?
My mama would kick your fucking ass, okay?
Or if my mom would put out a bagel in your brain, okay?
Terrible. I'm terrible.
Anyway, you like the music in here? Thank you beaches beaches, bitch. Thank you
Did you like the video or like the other a couple songs I made?
I mean one is about my little thin Scorpio and be it was like oh, he's making songs about me
Yeah, I did make a couple songs like probably three songs, but the pictures I was putting up like I made
One song I'm playing about her right, but the other songs are about little the songs live in Scorpio, right?
It's Swiss and Tea Time, yeah, let's bring it up.
I'm bringing Psyche back.
Sorry.
So what have I said about her?
Like, really nothing bad.
I mean, maybe today I have, but it's like, you know,
hey, what did she say about me?
Grifter, scammer, everyone in the chat yelling me,
like everyone in the chat is like,
oh, I'm a terrible person, right?
I'm not belittling anybody. Yeah, I was just there. Have I ever looked the incredibly malnourished and elder Rick from The Walking Dead?
I don't know, but who did he do? Who did he do? And
Moshe and
Am I Yiddish? No, I'm not Yiddish. I'm not. I'm not. I do. My sister is Jewish. I might have some Ashkenaz the
Ancestry
Yeah, I'm not belittling anybody else. I was always good to her, but it's like she said we're not fans anymore
I'm like fine. We're up like fine. Okay, so oh dude. I'm in trouble. I'm in trouble Vanguard. Oh, please Vanguard
Oh, I got clips coming out of you today. I got clips from it. There's clips out of you
Everyone go see van the Vanguard clips when it's in Vanguard clips. Let's play those right now
Let's play those right now
Vanguard wants to play with me today. Let's go
See
videos
I'm not I'm not I'm never in trouble, please
You're in trouble, okay
Let's see. I don't know if you're actually are in these ones, but I think you're in some
Do you want to see some clips guys? I did some surprises
I got some surprises for you
Remember when I say gloves are off that means the gloves are coming off
Okay, let's see
Just a few more
Okay, one, two, three, okay.
Ready?
Okay, here we go.
Dun, dun, dun, there's socks are off.
My shoes, okay, so here we go with some of these clips.
Okay, so share my screen and go to unmasking, okay.
And I'm going to put that on big, okay.
And chat and, okay, here we go guys.
I don't like dickheads like you, I don't like dickheads like you, we don't see anything apart from your own cult value, prick.
Bro, at the end of the day bro, you're mad as fuck because why?
You're mad as hell because why, bitch?
Fucking pussy.
Cause your shit is all fucked up, huh?
Is Trump came in and fucked your shit up
Not here right now they try to get take
I'm not
Doxin you're shooting a person who's innocent and you don't even know what the story is
I got shot in the leg and I'm telling you but I'm innocent
But yeah, that's just how that went, and I did that for a little bit, but once YouTube
started really kicking off, I really haven't done much with that fan site.
It's still there, but I just, yeah, you have to earn bunny points.
It's true, AC.
You do, actually.
I guess I could be farther along in my Playboy career,
but I kind of got started on YouTube,
and I just, I don't know, I just would rather do YouTube.
Well, I think YouTube has been a really awesome platform for you
I think you're just made for YouTube and people just love you your cat has like hundreds of people in it every night
You know, it's a while. I was a moderator for a while and we can address the elephant in the room of
Why I'm not a moderator anymore and that that's a good story, too
And it's and also it's all happy about size, but I think I think YouTube's for you. Okay. Go ahead
Okay, uh
Welcome Michael Michael. I'm on this. Oh, yeah, that that is that is uh, that is my friend
There's my from Michael already okay, okay, so we got you all there
But I remember that your pass on loves one pass on loved ones are always watching out for you are always
Wanting you to be happy. They love you. They're your ancestors. They're your father your mother
They're always there so never never doubt that you're not being washed over always remember you're being very loved, right?
You know, that's the thing that really amazes me is when I meet people and they're actually afraid of their own kin
People that they love they're afraid of the you know the ghost and I'm like
Why would you be afraid of them if they were one of your loved ones? Why would you do that?
Oh, that might be evil spirits claiming to be it's like, you know what, you know, because I actually had somebody
Ask me that and it's like, you know, you can tell how do you tell when anybody's evil?
You know, how can you tell when the person standing next to you is evil, right?
I mean especially back to the spirit realm is in the spirit realm
They have all this freedom to be in the spirit realm, but they're coming back to you to give you a message
And they because they love you because the love will always attract
Right, so one is coming back to talk to you. They're just your love. They're the same person
With a little bit more wisdom now because they're on the other side and going. Oh, I see
You know, they they have a little bit different viewpoint, but there's still your
They're almost exactly like they were in life except maybe with a little I want a divorce and he tells her no and
and Lilith doesn't want to admit that she's Lilith because she doesn't want the humans to like
Think badly of her. She doesn't like when anyone thinks badly of
So she's definitely not Lilith, and it's in a little bit of a sense.
Go back into your show a little bit, like I know you, so you have an old lady spirit
around you that helps you out with the tarot card readings, you're like a channel through.
Tell us about Cheryl a little bit.
So Cheryl is...
The character is based off of my grandma and you know my grandma was from old country and she
really
You know the the girls in my family. It was like clean. You know do this do that you have to do this
You're a woman you got to do that you got to do that and then to the boys
She was like, oh, let me make you a pie, you know, like I don't know
it's like the boys never had to do shit in my family and
She was an old religious woman with a mean gruff, you know that
Not to do what I have done
Spend your lives in synonyms misery
And the house of the rising sun
I've got one foot on the platform
the other of the trend I'm going down to New Orleans to wear that ball and not to do what I have done
I've got one foot on the platform, the other on the train, I'm gone, I'm gone, I'm gone,
So, uh, that ball and there was a terror reading that I did for you that someone thought it
was between me and you and I was like, no, it's not.
It's not and it was so funny because it was it was proved that I was right
But like, you know, I think people saw what went down and they just automatically thought like I was just like
Mad at you or something like that and I was annoyed and I was like we can't have this
But I was never like wishing
Bad upon you or any of that that like, you know, I know and also like
You know it what like we were talking behind the scenes all time
We were I was expressing my feeling you're expressing your feelings
We just like we had it all out and at the end where we said hey, we love each other
We're friends no matter what if I'm a mod or not or whatever what like modding is not important
It's like it's a friendship that's important and you are always there for me
You've always done from the heart care readings for me and I'd say anybody once a really
awesome terror reading
You know best the best deal on YouTube. I would say because she does
You also forgot giraffe lives matter activist and
You know
what the waffles lives matter to or the waffles waffles rights are human rights
right you know it's debatable whether or not human lives matter okay but what we
do know is the giraffe lives matter
great how are you doing tonight I love your hat I love you got the wings on
the camera angles like I like them.
And you're beautiful.
Thank you for so much for coming.
Thank you.
It's hard to portray that every episode.
I have over 300 episodes now that I've gone live.
They're like from three to seven hours long.
And...
You got to remember people come in and out in and out of the lives and they're always going what is going on and I could write a description and nobody reads the description, right?
Um, and by the way, also at paywiththeorcell.com I'm going to be making a blog to catch everyone up on everything that has happened because you know Emma's caught in purgatory and
she channels through an old lady spirit that Satan trapped in the house to be like special ops,
you know, like to keep an eye on Emma. And like, there's so many things that have happened.
So it's become quite the crazy story. And it's all on the premise of, you know, Lilith goes
to Satan and says. So when you promise your sister, I would be so upset. I'm not drunk.
I'm not drunk, Chrissy. Hey, Chrissy, we have a guest. Okay. Okay. I'm not drunk. Probably
gotty. You're not drunk. We gotty. Psyche. No, I'm not gotty. Oh, I'm sorry. Wrong one.
Wrong one. No, you just throw us in the same, in the same category. What's up?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I
Damn I took my eyes off the screen for a second so psyche. What's going on?
34 triple D all natural
Like mr. Big five
over and over
So this is such a certain thing
I'm just trying to yeah, I'm just chillin my girlfriend
Yeah
You should just be in that mr. Big Pipe's hit on page hit on page though. It's so cringy. Oh my god
Well, mr. Because they like that guy I think
Damn that guy's I don't like him at all
I think he's extremely
Acquired I
Don't like to use the word
But like I really really really dislike how he makes this face and he tongues like this fucking
Thanks, my oh, but he's just like oh yeah, and then blah blah blah is a I just want to fucking me
I mean it's fucked up face
But I just I don't like that
I like I don't that guy's disgusting and he used to be called mr. Big Poops
Hey
Yeah, it's a big poops
Probably have the same sentiment as a lot of these people in this chamber. I'm willing to bet
Well, he's just not a lot of people here being at all
You're like the guy in the passenger seat that's trying to claim you run Riverside
between them.
No.
You don't understand.
You're from Kentucky, bitch.
Shut the fuck up.
Originally from Chicago.
No, you're from Kentucky.
Shut the fuck up.
Listen.
I'm from Chicago.
I know a job I call there.
I'll just call it for the Mexican mafia here.
Shut the fuck up.
Bitch, you're from Kentucky.
The Bob's on here, motherfuckers, are you crying?
You better check fucking Kentucky's brother, baby.
You better go home and get the fuck out of here.
Man, don't be trying to hit him, man.
Don't be dissing the turkey man.
You better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you
Back then, if it's out there like that, I should be able to somebody should be able to quite meet me
They're saying they're saying I had this chick flash tits on my panel
I still have my panel from fucking five years ago. Like, okay
As much as people talk about it, like there's somebody should be able to show me where I could go see that right?
Well
Things were different back then
Nothing just appears on the internet. So if he was doing this shit, you're right. You're right about that. You're right about that
Yeah, no, I like some proof that he was doing this shit. Yeah, me too
By the way, if you tell me shut the fuck up again when I'm not talking, I'm gonna get really mad. I don't like that
Fuck you're saying fuck you and fuck you're saying motherfucker fuck you fuck you
Oh, yeah, what are you going to do?
No, I'm not. Yeah, he really passed out.
He's that fucking.
No, look, he's falling asleep.
Oh, my gosh.
Because he's going to fall asleep on the panel.
I'm just bringing my lullaby.
You have to fall asleep in the arms.
Say the N word.
I'm saying the N word.
Bitch, who you talking to though? Who you talking to bitch?
You, the trainee lover!
You a bitch though! You a bitch-ass, fake-ass nigga!
I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch, I'm a fake!
Cause I called you out, cause I called you out for being a trainee lover?
Come find me, say it to my face though though!
Oh yeah, I'ma fly to the UK, right?
To the face of a fake fraudulent Jamaican motherfucker!
You're welcome to come here and be Jamaican!
Yeah, you can't say it to my face cuz you're a bitch and you always will be of course you're far
Why would I go over there?
I love join your panel psyche and I just try to join betas, but like she's not even there like oh
Beta's taking a big shit
Like if you're going to be a professional like psyche right here. He's a professional. He's always on top of his job
Beta, I know I'm not here to cuss out beta, but you got to be more professional beta
You got you're being very unprofessional baby beta and we're not up here for it
your defense she can
Go to the bathroom and not have to she doesn't have to be there to pick up the pick up
Yeah, but she was going for like 20 minutes
Like if you got to use the bathroom don't go live if you're going to be gone for 20 minutes
You got to shit your brains out go do what you got to do
Sometimes I have to go when you gotta go you gotta go. What up and go
That's my boy vanguard right there man. That's like a brother to me vanguard. It's like a fucking brother to me, man
the
With your face. Oh, that's gonna be interesting Joe. You know that Joe, you know
I've been like you off almost every time someone was right today when they're like, oh Joe just like oh
There was Brando. He said Joe just like no
It's kicked off because he runs out of material and he gets nervous and that's a little so I know
Joe or it's a material. Okay. Anyway, go ahead. Go ahead
I'm just having a bit of a laugh with Joe, Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe
I've not come up here to disrespect you and your professional, the way you want to run
your channel, but anyway, I quite like you, never mind you kick me off now and then I
quite like you.
I like you, I mean, I don't just like, I like almost everybody like, because I can see people
are like, you know, just human beings and, but you know, some people just drive me a
cuckoo sometimes but you're fine now you're fine i don't think you've ever been that disrespectful
you're just a little bit arrogant in the world mate not arrogant um we were talking about your
novel the other night and you got the wrong idea you thought right because you're mentioning some
like stuff that it was kind of like not i don't know even if it works
Yeah
There was one word you mentioned and that's the country that the two nobles in and you you lost your shit
I just don't want stuff being mentioned about that stuff because it's not I don't think it's good for the
Algorithm so when I said, please stop talking about it. It'd be better to just stop talking about it or else, you know
Are you gonna apologize, but you didn't heal it for a tool the guy
I accept your apology, but the thing is it's like
Apologize and learn because I say I don't don't talk about it. Just don't talk about it. It's like cuz it's like it's my show
I have because you're like saying oh, yeah, I can talk about I'm allowed to it's like well
I asked you not to so that's why
Well, please don't talk about all the political narratives in front of me again
Well, I mean, I don't mean it's like there's certain things that are just not good for monetization
And so it's like I don't want to get involved in political talks that I'm not even like really understand very well
And so I can't contribute to it. I can't I can't
Moderate it. So
Again, I'm just Justin. Hello Patrick, New York
Yeah, so now I got beat as God like people after me now like, you know, Joe just came here trying to
Messes me and then like a beep beep person just put up some like you know some
Photoshopped staying with my face on it like you know me like smoking and the cats are in the room
I mean, it's like well, please like not a litter box inside. Oh, yeah, we were so funny
He probably uses a litter box instead of a toilet. That's why they're we're going to litter boxes
But I can't actually like I'm very well trained actually do not go to the bathroom in the house. I don't know what's so weird about that
apparently I'm
Little bit weird. I must be high as a kite. I wish I mean I wish what's the kite called? Well, I'm
I'm about to build a spliff. Is that okay with you psyche?
Of course
So how's the new friendship with Alexander Mears going?
Are you going to be doing more collaborations in the future?
Yeah, we actually, tomorrow we're doing the final of the three-part series.
We've filmed two parts of it.
There are on her channel AlexanderMears.com.
We had some great discussions.
The first one was about astrology and its roots.
I love how people can just declare themselves the winner. It's like it's like very three years old of you, but anyway
Yeah, so what was I saying? I'm sorry. I got distracted by some idiot
You were in more collaborations with Alexander Mears. Yeah, definitely. I love yeah, she's awesome. She's like, you know
She was on last not last night's the night before last night
And she's taking the day off today, so I'm excited for tomorrow, probably noon tomorrow, I think.
You know I know Alexander and I've been taught, well, I've seen her on the internet and communicated with her on panels for over four or five years.
Yeah, well, I've heard about her for a year, but I've been wanting to meet her and stuff and then you just click so well.
Hold on
Mods you can see who's being annoying in the chat you can just go ahead and do what you want with them
Maybe just time them out
Okay
Anyway, Vanguard. Yes. She's awesome
She's also like very understanding and things like that just because oh just people say oh, she's you know
She's she's no, but no you know
It's like she actually sees the real me and not just like you know some follower like most people like you know Rob and
Just like to blame you blame little chat bitches and everyone going
Nothing way on their own channel
So they have to like there go try to like bother me and my
Okay, I'm not here to diss you or her, but anyway, like I said, I've known, I've known about and communicated on panels like this with Alexander for over five years, so I know quite a bit, you know what I mean?
Yeah, when it was written, yeah, when I was in the spaceship. Okay, but yeah, go, Sumerian myth. I'll talk all about Kanaeiform. I know the oldest story in the world is Inan and descents into the underworld.
You said you know about cuneiform. Yeah, sounds what I
Don't I mean, I don't know it by heart. I just know I know the method of it and you know, I
I've read the translations. I think that they're kind of controversial as to how accurate the translations are
There's a little bit different than what I remember, but okay, hold on. I'll get it out of here
Come on come on mods. He's just annoying person. I'm just gonna kick him up
You're just going to time out in the naughty corner and oh beat is cooking
Well, be that go ahead and cook be that because I have a song about her biscuits and they're not very good
So have you ever read the Book of Enoch before?
I've never read it before.
Or at least, I've heard about the Book of Enoch.
Okay.
I mean, Vanguard, did you not hear?
There's a song playing.
You know, it's going on with the conversation.
Okay, I'll go back to you.
What's up? Go ahead.
Me and I was just asking if you ever read or heard about at least or watched some videos on the book of the band, book of Enoch
Are you talking about like
Let's take guys names not Zachariah Stitchin. Yeah, Zachariah Stitchin the guy that wrote the Zachariah Stitchin
No, no Enoch Enoch the book of Enoch
Yeah, of course I know the book of Enoch, you know, it's in the Dead Sea Scrolls and all that kind of stuff
but you know, that's also very controversial because
I don't know the density scrolls. It seems like a Psyop to me like they just like down them all these like, you know
perfectly preserved
You know scrolls and things like that inside this cave in the middle of nowhere like oh, let's go hide them
It's just like a perfect like, you know way to introduce more new more, you know pseudo-graphia into the into the mix
pseudo-graphia and that's very very pertinent very pertinent
the pseudo-graphia
You guys know the pseudographia, they're like these fake books in the Bible, they'll be like, you know, a new story about Adam and Eve will come out, like the last book of Adam and Eve, and it's like, it'll be written in old English, but it's like saying it's like from Hebrew, I mean, it's like, it's really pretty obvious, but you know, it's kind of interesting.
I can bring the video up if you want to see it, then it's sealed still, it's never been in it.
Have you seen that new discovery?
No, I mean, I don't know about what I could play out there, but I didn't see like when they found the King Tud's tomb
Okay, so I'm sure we're talking very recent is in the last
King Tud is very relatively recent too. You know, it's like with the last like a hundred years
What happened was
That wasn't the value of the Kings
So if you're buying an Egyptian ship, how do you think, what do you think the condition of everything on the side will be if you've kind of lost the Egyptian ship?
Right, right. Do you want me to bring this video for your own personal view, your own description?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm asking if I can tell you though, real quick.
Cause that was another-
You can chat, I'll go find this video for you.
Okay, I'll find it.
So here's the room that they found everything in.
Okay, I mean, look at this room.
Hold on.
See that room?
That room.
This is where everything is perfectly preserved inside of this room.
So let me just see if there's a better picture of the actual room when they opened it, because
everything is pretty freaking pristine and very pristine.
Okay, well when I saw the first picture of the room, it looked just basically like...
Look like a backstage of a
Movie like a prop room. It's like it's subfolded up. I don't know. It just looks like who else is here
Everyone's here. We have 34 people in the chat. You bury Dead Sea Scrolls a couple millennia go to troll people. Yeah, exactly
Yeah, well, they are trollish
Yeah, the Dead Sea Scrolls also someone said they were found my goat. Yeah worth there
There are some goat herder kids and then they like were playing like
slingshot or something and then I went into the cave it broke one of the jars
but then it's in there all preserved I mean it's like I didn't know they had all
this like paper back then it's like I know they're squirrels and stuff but
it's like you know the printing press was invented in like what 1560 or
something like this 1560 century so how do they have these huge long books like
I mean I just don't know where do these come from and it's like I know that they
the you know monasteries they would like you know write a Bible up by hand and
All the original stuff I just like where there was no publishing. How do they have these big books?
They have scrolls the scrolls must have been like humongous, you know, it's just like I just scroll with the whole Bible on
enormous
There you go. There's the most recent finding. It's not far from the Giza plateau. It's nowhere near the Valley of the Kings
and it's unopened, this is going to be very intriguing.
I'll watch it, I'll watch it, I'll watch it, my friend, I'll watch it, I'll watch it, I do want to watch it before I comment on it, thank you for recommending it, I do enjoy Egypt, but you know basically I'm very, whether the history or whatever they're saying is true or not, I love the mythology of it and the Egyptian gods are these very archetypal, powerful,
But they are, you know, and the animalistic, they have half, you know, usually have animal heads and things like that, which is, and then human bodies, which is saying something.
Well, that sort of hogs back to the fact of the Anunnaki really, doesn't it, is in Sumerian stuff.
The hybrids, the recruiting hybrids, with the DNA splicing and crossing the gorilla woman with the angel.
You heard about that
No, that's not a video would you share it with your community?
Yeah, I mean I will but I'm gonna watch it first my friend
But I'll have a look at it
Yeah man, it's only just been discovered, it's, it had it's seal stone still intact,
it was never raided, it was uncovered, very interesting, yeah.
Extremely interesting, extremely.
I got to go to bed. I'm just gonna let's see. So
I've got to stay awake I read mad Jim your mom might twat I'm talking about Jim mom might fella. He's a twat
Mad Jim mad Jim the mom might fella either hate them or you love them
Very what and
Yeah, that's it. It's gonna be it. Um, let's see what else I have to talk about. Let's see
Yeah, but oh it'll be as big as a complaint is that I'm playing clips for my own show. I mean, it's like
Can I fucking run my own show? I mean, I don't understand. Why are you having this guest on?
Why are you hiding this for it's like hello? Do I tell you how to run your show at one time?
I know believe someone's comment that I was basically like I'm you know an axe murderer
kittens and you know and you got mad at me I mean it's like so yeah 1440
Gutenberg press right and so how are they having these thousands year old
manuscripts published or in any capacity I just don't it doesn't make sense
wait the how could you see that when you believe in the Talbot
Well, I don't even believe the Talmud is it was an oral tradition that it was written
down much later than it was spoken, right?
It was an oral tradition.
So that goes along right along with it where it's like the oral tradition is more reliable
because that's what they actually practice rather than the Torah, right?
which is like
The Talmud is not very nice to
I know they're very mean to Jesus and they call Mary terrible names they call Mary a whore and
You can steal rape and murder including children if you're not if they're not Jewish
Well, it says that in the Bible too. It says that in the Bible in the Old Testament, but it's a different kind of God than in the New Testament.
The New Testament is like Jesus, and he's like really nice. The Old Testament, God's like an asshole.
He's like, he's like destroying everybody except his chosen people, and then like, and his chosen people were like, you know, very flawed individuals.
So anyway.
Yeah, but anyway, it's still a point of contention why a certain part of society thinks the better and
Control and rape murder and steal from anybody else. It's still a bit of a point of contention really isn't it?
Well, I mean, that's why I mean it's like
When criminals steal or steal or murder it's called, you know a crime when you know countries do it
It's called you know war or patriotism or whatever. So it's like a little bit of a different
Kind of thing and we might be considered terrorists in other places
They're just like they consider we consider people other people
I think that's a very broad term and you can paint on people you can't when we start paying our own citizens
That brings them into our own domestic people, into the ranks of the enemy
Which is very dangerous slippery slope to go down
I just warned people first they came for this person
I didn't do anything for then I came for this person
I didn't do anything and finally came that they came from me and it's like unless you're like a very
They've been very specific types I'm looking for unless you're very a very specific type there. Yeah, but I'm pretty interested in
having you around being a resource of sucker, like what they would say to you.
Right, can I just ask, did you go more on the spiritual aspect
because you have Jewish blood? You sort of went, no, I'm not accepting that,
I'll go some other other avenues.
No, I mean, I've studied already, I mean, the Christianity came out of
Judaism and it's even been this long.
out of a Hebrew with all the father Abraham's and the same patriarch.
And so they're very similar religions in a lot of ways like you know they're different
but they're similar.
I don't think I necessarily have Jewish blood but you know I'm very Jewish.
Yeah, my father has Ashkenazi, like a small percentage of Ashkenazi came from my father's chest, it didn't come from my chest.
So I don't know if I would just didn't get the genes or it's like it was just too small of a sample.
But my sister, I have a half sister that's 50% Jewish or 50% like Russian Jew and then...
No, that's Ashkenazi Jew, isn't it?
Yes, Ashkenazi, which is like, you know, it's different than the Sephardic, right?
I'm not allowed to be political here, but I could tell you a lot about asking how to use I really could
But I'm not the ones that were from the good certain area that like they were just they all converted
So they would would be taken over or something or the king converted everybody into this to that
And so they weren't they're not technically like the genetic Jews that are in the Bible
I think that's what I've heard but I'm not sure I got the story right, but
There was like the they converted this whole country not it's yeah exactly
But you know and I'll what are what are the NAZIs what it?
What is that stand for it's national socialists and what are so good so it's kind of interesting how I don't know
I won't get too far into that, but yeah, it's like a little bit
Weird kind of weird stuff going on in history. I don't know if I get the real story of what happened
It might be a quite different than what the official story is including great numbers
I just said can I just say set for a fact? Why have you got the eye of your foot and set there on your background?
Why do I have it? I designed a logo for my my company and I do enjoy the symbols of the eye
They also have it has like a labyrinth around it. I also have it tattooed on my own
Yeah, but you know you're in the eye of raw
Yeah, right there
I have the eye right there
Let's have a sit down
All right 13
See it
Was I there? No, were you there? Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Was anybody there? I don't know. It says nobody was there
It's like pretty easy to like they make up history that we take like snow white. It's like the fairy tale, right?
Or it was like a true story. I don't know. It's probably
makes more historical sense and some of the
Actual history it's my actual history is very fanciful. We're there. I don't know
But if you know where there was like, you know under a different brain and so how do we know our memories reliable?
Oh, we just know body right great brain
Can you ask one of your shutters a question, please? Thank you. Yes. Yeah
Anki, what about in you?
And they'll he's okay. You have a trap for him
His brother is his brother and his brother's and male the God of the winds and then and he's the God of the sweet water and
He was more of the earth God like the most or the water God to Poseidon and then and low was more of the Zeus the sky God
But just like in Greek mythology
Poseidon Hades and Zeus are a part of a trinity. We're basically the same God in different planes. Yeah
Do you believe, sorry, not that wrong, have you read much into North, sorry, North mythology?
Nordic, Nordic, yeah, like Odin and like, you know, like Valhalla and stuff.
It's basically the same, isn't it?
Oh, yeah, there's correspondences across all religions, like especially with the polytheistic religions, like the God, like there's always like the corresponding God.
Well, to say this, polytheistic was well before anything happened, until the Roman Empire went, we're fucked here.
And Emperor fucking, what's his name, fucking, fucking Constantine said, right, we're fucked here, we've got to change it all and we've got to become Christians.
But polytheism was part and always part of said religions wasn't it like Moses?
That was like the first like like worship of the single God the Sun God and that was like basically he's Akhenaten, right?
Who was like the first it was like the Pharaoh who was like, you know
He said worship the autumn which is like the Sun disc and that was like the first
Resistant documented, right? I
Don't know. We got what is in your mind banger. There's always a subtext. Like what are you trying to say?
What are you trying to say a lot of people will stay shit and it's like
Polotheism was well about before monotheism so go fuck yourself
No one's agree no one's disagreeing with that I think that the point because we know like you know they had monotheism
time they were worshiping Molok and they were worshiping their golden calf and all these
kind of different foreign gods like right there ishtar and all kinds of stuff so they
knew about the monotheism or the polytheism but basically they just changed it to the
sun worship of the sun which I think is wrong too because it's not like the sun is not the
only sun there's all it's just another star there's
and limited billions of stars and so I'd say we can worship maybe the stars in
general but not the specific sun. But they did not know the stars and the
night were all so stars as in suns. We just thought they were bright lights to it.
and
Before I go have you watched much or also sort of researched much about three one atlas I
Haven't but I want to ask you a question. What was it like?
What was it like starring in mrs. Doubtfire?
Wow, it was a fucking nightmare for the makeup
Yeah, oh, you're you play you did play mrs. Doubtfire, right?
I
Played black fucking servant
You know what why did you have to go there?
Like what is that? I mean, it's like what is that even mean? It's just racist. I mean, it's just racist for the sake of being
Dismention in what happened in the movie. There was a black
I don't remember the black I don't remember black women and this is that fire playing in the
Significant role. What was her part?
Um, right you like cats, don't you?
No, I don't like cats. I only have
Well, do you think that Tom and Jerry had a problem?
Yeah, they were really bad at like all the Tom is really I mean who's the cat Tom?
Yeah, Tom was really bad at catching mice and
Then I think that that mouse was on some kind of like emphatomine or something. He was so fast
But yeah, I think they had probably had drug problems Tom on heroin and Jerry on
Methamphetamine, what do you think?
mate I wouldn't know much about my thumb that I mean because I'm currently not
serving I wasn't in the second world war and I'm not a crack head or a fat head
or a thing but you do you do you do is you just do you start a coat right?
yeah I'm like I know how did I know that how do I just know what why do I know
things like how do I just know that you're a coaxing sort of I just knew it
What me it you said I like cook. I don't like cook
Well, it's different than the drug. I mean everyone likes nobody likes color really everyone likes like the drug
Right. No, I'm right. Okay. Hold on. Everyone likes to code the drink and then nobody likes
But nobody likes it. Why is it so expensive?
Never mind never mind
Anyway vanguard, let's get back to the common Jerry
No, let's get back to common Jerry
Right the common Jerry thing right was it really?
But the old was out of black with stockings this flip is on it
He was a transvestite. That was an inspiration for the Rock Your Picture show
was Tom and Jerry, didn't you know that?
Everyone knows that.
You want to know what my childhood was like?
A lot rougher than yours, New York.
I ain't grew up in New York, I grew up in Los Angeles,
which is probably a lot rougher than...
Marriott England.
Where they don't even have guns.
Again, but you know, the black woman with the stockings on in the Tom and Jerry fucking movies, that's not racist.
She's not a black woman. Her stockings were black, but she was white under them.
No, she was a black woman. She was like the...
They just showed her above the waves. They just showed her stockings.
Of course, they wouldn't allow that back then, but her voice and her fucking socks and sand those went away.
No, the lady of the house is not
She was it was probably her house. I mean it's like but I think it was probably like
Yeah, I don't know
Vanguard what are you talking like why are you trying to make me talk about these things? I mean, right?
I'm not here to troll you I will disappear and let you all talk
I mean, thank you. Thank you. Okay. Perfect. I love it. Thank you. Have a good day
I'm just gonna you can say up you left
Well, Vanguard, it's fine. I mean your friend of the show kind of
Anyway, how we do I know it's I know it's here. I know it's here. I have no idea what we put
I have a beat-up apology song, but she even listened to this one
your critiques rain down harder than a hurricane breeze I don't want to feel
worthless don't want to feel small be to take your foot off my neck that's all I
made that art I thought it was rad didn't know it would make you so
Like a guilty pop every time I post
Put off mine
I wish we could! I wish we could!
I don't know. It doesn't seem very open to...
It's a pistachio? A pistachio?
Whispers, psyche laying velvet night, her lover came with hidden wings, a secret kept from sight.
Trust the darkness, don't betray, love is more...
What's at stake?
Psyche child of mortal
But trust had torn them far apart
And Psyche wandered through the world with grief carved deep in
I don't know
What are you thinking? We're gonna be mad. We're gonna be mad. Okay
What do you do? It's a piss take. Um
Let's see Vanguard turns up again pretend we were communicating planning things against him. Oh, wow Jim. I
Want to hear the worry in his voice
Please bye. Yeah, bye. Bye everybody. Yeah, well good luck with that because
What me worry
What me worry, I don't even care worrying won't get me anywhere